Heroes aren't born... They're cornered.
Bullies is a action, drama, thriller film directed by Paul Lynch.
When the peaceful Morris family move to a small town and buy the town
grocery store, they run afoul of the Cullen family.
The Cullen's have been bullying the town's folk for years, and now they
are harassing the Morris family every chance they get.
Matt meanwhile meets and starts seeing a lot of Becky who also likes him.
Unfortunately her last name is Cullen, and when the rest of the family finds out about their
relationship, they decide to get even, and their harassment is elevated to vicious assault.
Matt Morris, played by Jonathan Crombie.
Becky Cullen, played by Olivia D'Abo.
Jenny Morris, played by Janet-Laine Green.
Clay Morris, played by Stephen Hunter.
Will Crow, played by Dehl Berti.
Jimmy Cullen, played by Bernie Coulson.
Bullies is a 1986 Canadian action drama thriller film directed by Paul Lynch and
starring Jonathan Crombie, Janet-Laine Green, Stephen Hunter and Olivia d'Abo.
In a story that has elicited occasional comparisons to Romeo and Juliet, a vendetta arises from the forbidden
relationship between a teenage girl, whose clan terrorizes a small town, and the son of a newly arrived family.
The film received polarized reviews, which often praised its craftsmanship
while questioning the ethics of its vigilante violence.
The film explores themes of farm, small town, rape, sadism, fishing.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.